export const data = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        option1: "Virtual Dom",
        option2: "Original Dom",
        option3: "Both A and B",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        option1: "Server-side framework",
        option2:"user interface framework",
        option3:"both a and b",
        option4:"none of the above",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components fro outside",
        option1:"Render with arguments",
        option2:"setState",
        option3:"PropTypes",
        option4:"props",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Who created React.js",
        option1:"Jordan Mike",
        option2:"Jordan Walke",
        option3:"Tim Lee",
        option4:"Jordan Lee",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "In which language is React.js written",
        option1:"Python",
        option2:"JavaScript",
        option3:"Java",
        option4:"PHP",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is babel?",
        option1:"JavaScript compiler",
        option2:"Javascript interpreter",
        option3:"JavaScript transpiler",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the commond used to create a react app.",
        option1:"npm install create-react-app",
        option2:"npm install -g create-react-app",
        option3:"install -g create-react-app",
        option4:"None of the above",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
        option1:"3000",
        option2:"3306",
        option3:"3030",
        option4:"8080",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        option1:"1",
        option2:"2",
        option3:"3",
        option4:"4",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "A state in React.js is also known as?",
        option1:"The internet storage of the component",
        option2:"External storage of the component",
        option3:"Permanent storage",
        option4:"All of the above",
        ans: 1
    },
]